=Love Actually S5=
(Previously)
The semi-mature journey...
(Confession Moment)
It is sparked by the pull of destiny.
We all believe
that someone is meant for us.
(I prepared this necklace for you.)
(Amazing moment.)
What a beautiful moment.
So sweet.
(Nothing to worry about them.)
(I'll stake my fortune on it.)
(So steady.)
(Prince and princess.)
Thank you for choosing me so firmly.
And thank the universe
for bringing Lu Bingkun to me.
You can
be your true self in front of me,
like a child.
Ruita, I like you.
Will you be my girlfriend?
After so many times,
it still feels so good.
(Everything was just right.)
(Oh, my!)
(This is so romantic.)
(Xiao-Pei Duo.)
You are so beautiful.
"You are so beautiful."
These two should be solid, right?
(Look. That smile is)
- (sweet.)
- (Sweet.)
(Yeah.)
Nothing can go wrong.
Nothing can go wrong?
Don't worry. Nothing can go wrong.
You promise?
I'll stake my fortune
for the next ten years on it.
(Ten-year fortune)
There's no need for that.
Alright, whatever Mr. He says.
Nothing can go wrong.
(Steady)
I don't usually write.
You know?
I've written all the words
I would write in a year
in this notebook.
To Xuan.
As I always say,
you are the most special in the house.
Your personality, experiences,
behavior, and everything
have made you who you are today.
What makes you shine
comes from your reluctance
to speak too easily,
your refusal to show off,
and your unwillingness
to follow the crowd.
You don't talk much
about yourself in front of people,
which adds to your mystery and charm.
You exercise. You love life.
You enjoy life.
And
your skin tone
is something I really envy.
I've always wanted that skin tone.
You look so cool.
Nice outfit.
Oh, my.
Why are you so good-looking?
I'm so envious of her skin tone.
But I might
get a little paler in winter.
But as soon as summer arrives,
I'm like this.
You're a chameleon.
(Xiao is quite humorous.)
(I'll bask in the sun)
(to get a bit darker.)
(Xiao Wentao
is deeply attracted to Xuan.)
(Outpouring of love.)
But I think your eating habits
are a bit bad.
Why is this guy nagging?
We're back to square one.
What you said today
is exactly what you said
in the first episode.
Nagging.
He's the most down-to-earth.
You know?
Seriously.
This is his personal trait.
But I think your eating habits
are a bit bad.
You don't eat much at mealtimes,
but you can keep snacking non-stop.
I hope you can
slowly change
to a better diet
for your health.
Here is
another important thing.
A healthy diet
can preserve your beauty.
Okay, accepted.
Okay.
And
our interaction
gives me zero pressure.
We can stay silent
if we have nothing to say.
It doesn't
make us
feel awkward.
We've never felt that way.
So I drew
fifty percent and...
(Don't look)
Don't look at my handwriting. It's ugly.
(Secretly showing you guys)
(It's alright.)
(It's not that ugly.)
Fifty percent and fifty percent.
And this is a scale.
I think
this is what I feel between us.
There is a balance.
Such balance matters a lot
to me.
At the rapeseed flower field,
we had our first
in-depth conversation.
That was a good start
for us
to truly get to
know each other.
Wake surfing.
You helped me unlock
a new skill.
I was sitting on the boat.
The moment I saw you let go of the rope,
I found you so cool.
You were really cool.
At that moment,
I found you
very charming.
I recreated the painting
you tore apart.
I took a photo of it
with my phone.
It should be this one.
Nice painting.
Really?
Yeah.
(Extremely happy)
(By Xiao Wentao)
Nice painting.
It's nothing like that.
(By Jia Peixuan)
You could say.
Fifty percent. It grasped the idea.
(That's so easy.)
Is it fun?
Yeah.
So cozy.
(And about the electric bike...)
Let go here.
Just lean on me.
No rush.
Don't go fast.
(It wasn't great.)
(But I think it was a great experience.)
Why?
If you hadn't fallen that day,
our impression of that day
wouldn't have been so deep.
What?
Sorry.
Your sacrifice
made our memory of that day.
And about the tennis,
I wrote,
"I'm lame."
"But I don't accept it."
"I hope that next time
I can make you leave the court crying."
So arrogant.
(A clashing couple.)
And at the music restaurant,
I played terribly.
How is this guy so handsome?
A beam of light shone on you.
You're making me shy.
I'm getting shy.
(You've said more than once)
(that you saw me shining.)
Glowing.
All sparkling, you know?
Shining from every angle.
(I may have achieved something)
(in my career path)
(throughout these years.)
(But I still look forward)
(to positive feedback)
(from those around me.)
Beautiful.
So what you said to me
was really important.
It can sustain me for a long time.
And I'd like to invite you
to watch my formal performance.
(They really appreciate each other.)
I'll get started.
First question.
What animal is the quietest when angry?
Gorilla.
Because gorillas get "quietly furious".
[*Sounds like "pounding chests"]
So I chose a notebook like this.
I've been preparing this
since the day before.
I went to the city
and printed
all the photos
of you
and us
on my phone.
My original intention
was to record
every single moment we shared
from when we first met in the house.
So,
I actually wrote
until almost 5 AM.
The first time
I felt a flutter for you
was back when we were
in the rapeseed flower field.
I took this photo of you.
You look really cool.
I wrote "Rapeseed flower, talented".
(Rapeseed flower, talented)
I drew Peppa Pig.
Peppa Pig.
And then,
we took a photo together
on our way to the supermarket.
And I wrote down our dialogue.
"Do you eat rice cakes?"
"I'll have some if someone makes them."
"Will you have some?"
"Will you make them for me?"
"Yeah, I will."
"Then I'll have some."
I wrote,
"So the push-and-pull started then."
Then you asked me,
"Do you want to play tennis?"
I said, "Sure."
Then you said,
"Should we ask everyone to play?"
But actually, I didn't want to play
with the others.
I only wanted to play with you.
The next day we went for an outing
together.
We squeezed under that umbrella.
I felt
that we were quite close.
I was a bit shy.
That day, I also felt a flutter.
(One, two, three.)
Are you doing this on purpose?
No.
Are you messing with me?
You're a bit heavy.
(Then in the evening, I found out)
(that our date was due to)
(a task the night before.)
(But at that time,)
(I didn't notice that task at all.)
(I only remember)
(sitting on the balcony,)
(seeing you smiling)
(and waving at me,)
(telling me to go out.)
(At that moment, I also felt a flutter.)
(Because of your smile.)
When I went out, I was so happy
(Head-banging happy)
that I stupidly bumped into the wall.
(Then later,)
(we went to Sanya.)
(When you held my hand,)
(the world)
(went quiet.)
(I only heard my heartbeat.)
(And here I wrote,)
("My heart skipped a beat.
What about you?")
(My heart skipped a beat)
(Then it was the day)
(you were so handsome you glowed.)
Beautiful.
(I am indeed)
(attracted to talented people.)
(I can't help it.)
(I keep approaching you.)
(Sometimes our bodies
are more honest than words.)
(I think Xuan really needs favoritism.)
(Xuan dares to love.)
(Let's do it again.)
I keep winning.
You can't beat me anyway.
You're the one who's losing. Not me.
Anyway, I won.
So sweet.
She really remembers every detail.
And this card is
from that day we played tennis.
You didn't give it to me last night.
I didn't give it to you.
I wrote a "Summon Anytime" card.
Teleportation magic.
On a designated target.
Make that person show up instantly.
Duration: 24 hours.
At any time.
It's for you.
(Summon Anytime.)
Xiaowen
is over the moon now.
So captivated.
She's got this nagging man
under her thumb.
There are actually
many photos
I haven't included.
Your talent.
The way you play the trumpet.
Your focused look.
The way you cook.
The way I fed you food.
Yeah.
I find those things
very charming and attractive.
On one hand,
you're like a child,
messing around with me,
laughing with me.
On the other hand,
you're extremely mature.
You sense my emotions.
You see how defensive I get.
So I think of you
as a man.
That's how I feel.
The last paragraph
is both for you
and me.
It says,
"If you refuse to love
because you're afraid
of failing and getting hurt,
if you refuse to possess something
because you're afraid of losing it,
then you may avoid pain."
"But you also lose the most vibrant
and brilliant energy in life,
love."
(The most vibrant
and brilliant energy: Love)
Here's what I want to say.
We live in different cities.
There is a distance between us.
But I think
we have plenty of opportunities.
I might come to Shanghai
for performances, events,
or even just for fun.
I will definitely
strive for more opportunities.
And I feel
that
this city seems less strange
with you here.
I think
things might be
a little different in real life
from when we're on a show.
So, will you let me see
your true look in real life?
Yes, I will.
Xiao Wentao, I like you.
This is a confession, right?
Is my fortune safe?
Xiao Wentao, I like you.
Xiao Wentao.
She said she likes you.
Answer her.
(I didn't expect)
(to hear her say that.)
(I was deeply moved at that moment.)
(And I became more determined.)
(I want to get to know her better
in real life.)
(We've spent 20 days together.)
(I know I like him.)
(That's something beautiful.)
(Xuan.)
Sis.
Unbelievable.
Pretty.
Okay, got the shot.
What is this?
I'm really speechless.
Ten.
What ten? Two.
Reward for you.
You think it's too heavy?
You talk too much.
(I've been divorced,)
(and I have a child.)
We need to get groceries. Yeah.
(Be careful.)
(Slowly.)
Step here.
I'll catch you.
Am I awesome?
Praise me.
We went to the supermarket
just to buy rice cakes.
Slowly.
No rush.
Don't go fast.
Let go here.
Just lean on me.
Hang in there.
Let's buy some bubble tea.
Bubble tea.
Something like that.
It's like
pressing on my nerves.
Massage.
He even gave me a massage.
So beautiful.
It went into my mouth.
(Just kiss each other.)
(Let me see that.)
I prepared something for you.
I've been holding on to it
since yesterday.
It's a cup
and a little cat.
There's another cat inside the cup.
So cute.
Thank you.
Thank you?
What else can I say?
What should I say?
What did I say?
Don't say thank you.
Here.
Let's go.
(It says Xiaowen on it.)
(Is that your name?)
(Yeah.)
(I'm Jia Peixuan.)
(Love is the boiling point under the ice,
Jia Peixuan, Xiao Wentao)
(The playful banter
wrapped in a scorching undercurrent)
(Beneath the frozen past,
lava is churning)
So they're a couple now, right?
Right?
Did I save my money?
(Ten-year fortune)
Ten years of fortune.
Is his fortune safe?
Is my fortune safe?
It doesn't count.
They only agreed to meet.
(What?)
Then what about my...
Your ten-year fortune...
No.
It's going to be a serious confession.
Just watch.
(Next one)
It's going to be a serious confession.
(I'm quite looking forward)
(to how I will react)
(as well as)
(what he will tell me.)
(Time flies.)
(A month has passed.)
(We're standing here again.)
Liu.
(To meet the person from the notebook)
(feels quite magical.)
I bet they'll kiss each other.
I bet on Mr. He's ten-year fortune.
(Again?)
I dare to bet on this.
I definitely dare to bet on this.
We're going to give them
a wedding gift.
Yeah, we are.
Yeah, it will be a serious confession.
Hello.
Flowers for you.
(The bossy CEO's love is intense.)
(Bossy CEO's love.)
(Her hands aren't big enough.)
Can you carry it?
I can carry it.
Put it aside.
Okay.
I really like it. Thank you.
(Zhou is quite handsome today.)
(Zhou Youling suddenly became shy.)
(Nervous.)
Let me start.
Then you go first.
(What's wrong?)
Why, before even starting...
First meeting,
from the moment you came in,
as we chatted, we discovered
many coincidences,
making me feel absurd yet subtle.
My taste isn't very picky,
but I do
have a few little quirks.
But I didn't expect that we,
on the path of gourmet tasting,
could travel together.
I feel I can't wait
to unlock
more exclusive flavors with you.
We both love the tranquility
of old streets and alleys.
Finally, I met you,
fellow traveler.
You always said before
that you couldn't understand
my roundabout delicacy.
But along the way,
you slowly got closer to me,
trying to understand my silence,
accepting
my indirect expression.
Do you remember
the seaside sunrise we missed?
Actually, I've always remembered,
and I've always been
looking forward to it.
I want to wait for
another leisurely sunrise,
and stand with you
in the morning's first sea breeze.
When the daylight spills
over the coastline,
let the waves dissolve
all the regrets between us.
I think meeting you,
compatible and in sync,
is unexpected
and also destined.
Thank you.
And
this is for you.
Thank you.
Rose dog.
As for this little dog,
the reason
I want to give it to you is that...
when we returned to Shanghai that day,
the first thing I saw
when I got back to my room
was that blue little dog
we got at the market.
I had many regrets in Hainan.
Actually, at that time,
my mood was very down.
And I kept,
after returning to the house,
comforting myself,
trying to calm down.
But when I opened the door
and saw that blue little dog,
I really felt that...
I didn't want to leave any more regrets.
So I think
that blue little dog
was a turning point.
I think
I'm very grateful to myself
for bravely taking that step.
So I want to
give this meaningful
little dog
to you.
It represents my bravery.
Thank you.
This is indeed touching.
(This hug)
(also resolved some
of her small grievances.)
Do you have anything else to say?
I have a lot more.
Okay.
Someone said,
all unexpected gentleness
is a destined encounter.
And my fate with you,
from the beginning
of this semi-mature journey,
was quietly engraved
with an exclusive mark.
The starting point of the story
is a randomly drawn destined card.
Your favorite color is blue.
You decorated your home in blue.
When seeing navy blue clothes,
she can't take her eyes off them.
(In the vast sea of people,)
it happened that you and I
got the same bond.
With this fateful pull,
we started our first date.
From the first glimpse of you
at the piano as I walked in,
you've been the irreplaceable highlight
of my journey.
But our story wasn't smooth.
Along the way,
there was hesitation, doubt,
and our wandering.
You wavered,
and I also, because I couldn't see
your feelings clearly,
chose to step back and turn away.
During those days when we drifted apart
slowly in silence,
I never truly let go of you deep down.
(Clearly in the same space,)
(yet we deliberately kept distance.)
(Every moment of passing by)
(was a struggle and regret
hidden deep inside.)
(I thought maybe we would stop here.)
Are you going out tomorrow?
To fulfill a regret.
Whose regret?
My regret.
(Until the moment you
took the initiative to walk towards me,)
(all the barriers instantly dissolved.)
(It's really because of love.)
It's really love.
All of this doesn't matter anymore.
Love can conquer all.
Yes.
Slowly getting closer,
we let down our guard.
Later, with deeper understanding,
we kept marveling at our similarities.
Me too.
Without forcing,
just to get closer to each other.
In those casual moments
in our interactions,
the emotional eye contact,
and the subconscious little gestures,
my heart flutters never stopped.
Starting from a destined card,
to the sincerity of a two-way rush.
Along the way,
we finally understand
the initial card
with the same preference for blue
was never a coincidence.
It was a foreshadowing planted by fate.
Fated love
means no immediate
lifelong commitment at first sight,
but persistent mutual devotion
through doubts, delays,
and missed encounters.
Favoritism. There must be favoritism.
Our story has just begun.
Thank you for this encounter.
In the years to come,
I want to pursue our passion
together with you,
continue writing this destined fate.
Thank you.
After going around in circles,
it's still her. That's great.
And
during this time in the house,
I have many photos of you on my phone.
So I took these photos
into a profile
for you.
Very thoughtful.
Super thoughtful.
With my skills,
no need to edit the original photos.
Not bad.
It's pretty good, right?
Really not bad.
Okay, stunning.
This is so boyfriend POV.
Thank you.
Impressive.
Just be casual.
(First matching couple photo
in the same frame)
(First time taking photos
of each other)
(First time sneaking a photo)
What are you doing?
I don't want to.
Alright, let's take another one.
(After getting the task,
you rushed up to take a photo with me)
But it's pretty cold
to go out for a walk at this hour.
Babe.
It's lying on my feet.
(First official date, fishing, archery, go-karting, cuddling dogs)
Absolutely stunning.
(Caught a glimpse of your cuteness)
Where did you get the blanket?
Share.
(I care more about the feeling
of being favored.)
(Then you want to)
(get to know me deeply?)
(Or to get to know everyone deeply?)
(If you want to)
(get to know each other deeply,)
(I can)
(get to know you deeply alone.)
(It feels like our communication)
(is a bit off.)
(I don't know if you can feel)
(my anxiety.)
(In our relationship,)
(there is hesitation and holding back.)
(Then just forget it.)
(If you are holding back,)
(I think we should just forget it.)
Let it be.
But I haven't even finished speaking.
Forget it.
♪I understand, beautiful things
always fear being let down♪
♪I just don't want you
to feel angry later on♪
(During those silent days, I was paying attention to you.
Pretending to film Xiaowen, but actually...)
Quick, Big Bro is here.
Quick, take a nice photo of us.
(This is behind the mirror.
Pretending to film everyone, but actually)
(Pretending to film dinner, but actually)
(Watching you wash dishes alone)
♪When you see all this clearly,
and if you still feel comfortable♪
But I respect your choice.
I mean, if you
don't want to go out tomorrow,
I can completely accept that.
I haven't even said it yet.
Why do you keep saying
I don't want to go out tomorrow?
♪If you want to fall in love with me,
please think it through first♪
My creative urge is back again.
(A beautiful start, Pizza)
♪When you accept all this,
the good and bad, sort it out clearly♪
♪Then give me your hand,
I will hold it tightly♪
Then you ate a lot of chicken poop.
♪Besides the darkness♪
♪There is also a glimmer floating♪
♪Who is perfect?♪
♪Who hasn't been humbled and stained?♪
Hello.
I'm Youling.
I'm Liu.
Liu.
Yes, Liu.
This is you.
Yes, it's me.
(I truly wish them happiness.)
(This part is truly)
(intense and passionate.)
So annoying, really.
So heart-fluttering.
Really?
And then, looking at it this way.
It's the ending.
And there are
four more.
(What's wrong?)
(What did she see?)
These are the places you said
you wanted to visit together.
(Take me to Chulalongkorn)
Made with AI tools.
(Go with me to the London Eye)
(London Eye.)
(Go with me to the EDM festival)
(Watching the sunrise with you)
These are about imagining the future.
I knew you wanted to go
when we were in Hainan.
I wanted to ask you
to go that day too,
but we didn't make it in the end.
We'll replace these four photos
with real ones
in the future.
Yes, we will.
Definitely we will.
And there's a thick book behind.
We can finish writing it together.
Yes, it's for you.
Thank you.
Do you like it?
Wipe some more.
Another one.
Zhou is really thoughtful.
Zhou is really...
And then
I was thinking about
whether to give you
something practical.
And after a few days
of observation, I noticed
your phone screen protector was cracked.
So I got you a screen protector.
So practical!
Thank you.
Super practical.
I can use it right away.
And
maybe just a screen protector
would be too shabby.
See, he anticipated it.
So I'm also giving you a phone case.
Thank you.
You're setting me up for a joke here.
No wonder you asked me that day
what phone model I had.
Yeah.
That's the reason.
Then what's your phone model?
Phone model?
Let me see.
It seems to be 14 Pro.
Then I bought the wrong one.
(Bought the wrong one.)
(Even bought the wrong case.)
(No.)
(He surely kept
some tricks up his sleeve.)
It's okay.
I was actually thinking
of getting a new phone recently.
Alright.
Then I'll get you a new phone.
(He's so annoying.)
Look, isn't he annoying?
- I said he wouldn't be like that.
- You're so bad.
He wouldn't stop like that.
Enough.
- They have us wrapped around their fingers.
- This trick.
This gift-giving process
is the same as their relationship,
ups and downs.
And it's the blue you like.
Navy blue.
Don't cry.
You're crying
even if I'm giving you a phone?
I got the biggest storage.
I hope in the future you can
take more photos and videos of us.
Thank you.
I like it very much.
Stop crying.
Come on, Zhou Youling.
Thank you.
So beautiful.
Then don't cry.
I've always felt that...
I've told you before.
I feel like I am
a very ordinary person.
I feel that as I came here,
the favoritism you gave me
makes me feel that I'm not ordinary.
You are the best.
Thank you.
For coming close to me,
fulfilling me, accepting me
and completing me.
When we were in Hainan,
I kept overthinking.
I thought of many possibilities.
But I
just didn't dare
to hope for a future together.
I think
because of you,
I now dare to start hoping
for our future.
I dare to look forward to the future.
Thank you, Zhou Youling.
I like you.
♪Out of the seven billion people
in this world♪
♪There's only you♪
I like you too.
The wait was worth it.
Truly, some waiting is worth it.
Then can you be my girlfriend?
♪Baby, you're the only one♪
I don't want to cry anymore.
No more crying.
(This is also very romantic.)
(Burying herself in his arms.)
Did you say yes?
Yes.
♪Out of the seven billion people
in this world♪
♪There's only you♪
♪Almost a million words
that I could say♪
♪But none of them will do♪
♪So many years that I have lived♪
♪But it feels like I've just begun♪
♪Surrounded by numbers♪
♪Numbers, numbers, numbers♪
♪You're the only one♪
Look up.
He said look up.
Look up. Zhou.
Zhou.
No, I'm too shy.
Let me see.
See what?
See how...
Here it comes?
♪Out of the seven billion people
in this world♪
♪There's only you♪
Hey, brothers.
- I'm already dying of laughter.
- Save me.
They are really like a romantic drama.
They are so much like a drama.
♪Almost a million words
that I could say♪
♪But none of them will do♪
♪So many years that I have lived♪
♪But it feels like I've just begun♪
Are you cold?
Now you've really cried your makeup off.
♪You were unexpected♪
♪When our lips connected♪
♪I was resurrected♪
♪Never found a love like you♪
♪Love like you♪
(At that moment,
my mind kept flashing back)
(the fragments of life in the house)
(over the nearly one month)
(and thinking about
the word "destined".)
♪Love like you♪
(I just felt that)
(this relationship with Zhou Youling)
(had ups and downs)
(and eventually came full circle.)
(And in the end,)
(we ended up together.)
(I feel like it was arranged by fate.)
(It's a very unforgettable experience.)
(I hope that)
(after deeper contact
and communication,)
(we can have a better future.)
Let's go.
♪Out of the seven billion people♪
(Love is the only solution Xu Lvyang Zhou Youling)
This is so satisfying to ship.
(She solved
the misunderstanding equation)
(He gave the definition of favoritism)
This ending is so joyful.
(A two-way rush always
needs one solution)
(Many times we brushed past each other.)
(If we finally meet,)
(then maybe this is fate.)
(Even if we want to avoid it,)
(we will still end up)
(going down the path of intersection.)
(Whenever you meet the right person,)
(It's always right.)
(It has a strong sense of destiny.)
(Every person in this world)
(should have a person
on the same frequency.)
(And you deserve to be loved.)
(And that person deserves
to be loved by you.)
(A red thread in the unseen world)
(entwins you and me.)
(After all the twists and turns...)
- (Finally we meet.)
- (This is destiny.)
(Guided by destiny, love sincerely)
So shocking.
We also wish
Liu-Zhou couple well, right?
Love is just so beautiful.
Many people like their
ups and downs
with many stories
and many experiences.
All very earnest.
Back and forth,
and then finally confessing
"I like you".
Yes.
And there's another couple,
(Xiao Wentao and Jia Peixuan, Xiao-Pei Duo)
Xiao-Pei Duo.
During this offline period,
they get to know each other better.
Just like Youling and Liu,
they are also continuing to get to know
each other offline.
So what's the ending?
We don't know either.
What kind of ending is it?
Let's watch the "Love Actually"
Extra episode.
Can we ask them in person?
Are we going to ask them face to face?
Will I see them in person?
I'm very nervous.
Honestly, I'm very nervous
(Quickly sit up straight)
seeing the real people.
What are you nervous about?
I don't know.
I'm nervous seeing them.
It's not like you're the one dating.
(Then I'll leave)
(Quietly leaving)
I'm going to hide.
You guys can meet them first.
What exactly are you nervous about?
It's not like you're getting married.
No.
If the couple you ship
appears in front of you,
won't you get scared?
Why would I be scared?
Who do you ship?
I ship them all.
Hello.
(Are they really here?)
Hi, ladies and gentlemen.
You're so good-looking!
Zhou, Zhou is here.
Hello.
Hi.
So beautiful.
As expected,
all so handsome and beautiful.
All good-looking.
Welcome.
Alright, let's switch seats first.
Then, we'll chat properly.
Once again, a round of applause
for all the couple guests
of Love Actually S5.
Let's have each pair
say hello to everyone.
Hello everyone.
This is Ruita of the Yi-Lu Duo,
the lady with a young girl vibe,
in Love Actually.
Just now during the confession,
that's not how you introduced her.
Listen up, everyone.
This is my girlfriend.
Who is she?
She's my baby.
Okay.
It's heating up.
This is Lu of the Yi-Lu Duo,
a gentleman with a mature vibe,
in Love Actually.
My "byba".
What?
My support?
Our nickname on WeChat
used to be "Baby",
but we thought it was a bit cheesy.
So we reversed it.
"Byba".
Hi, everyone.
This is my "forced love" boyfriend,
Zhou Youling.
"Forced love".
We like it.
Hi, everyone.
This is my "Loves to battle" girlfriend,
Liu.
"Loves to battle"?
You don't understand?
It's a popular saying.
"Forced love" and "Loves to battle"
are a pair.
It's a very compatible style.
Yes.
(Perfect match)
Hi, everyone.
This is
my girlfriend, Xihui.
When did this happen?
We talked for two days
after the show.
Maybe there were
some misunderstandings on the show.
Then after talking, we
got together.
We like this kind of
straight-to-the-heart thing.
Hello, everyone.
This is my
obedient "husband-material boyfriend",
Ling Lizheng.
I like it.
Hello, everyone.
This is my boyfriend,
Xiao Wentao.
(Keep the fortune)
- My fortune is safe. - My fortune is safe.
My fortune is safe.
Why is your fortune safe?
- Why?
- On you two,
I bet my ten years of fortune, you know?
He bet ten years of fortune.
You better stay together well.
(Ensure your prosperity)
I must help you keep this fortune.
(I'm counting on you)
Stay together well.
And this is my girlfriend and big sis,
Peppa.
"Girlfriend and big sis".
Did you also talk after the show and...
Yes.
Perhaps after two or three days
of leaving the house.
You all needed those two days.
(Want to see, but can't)
This process was necessary.
It's impossible without it.
(Almost there, but not quite)
Since everyone has so many
curious questions,
there's no need to hold back.
Anyway, they are here in person.
Everyone can ask freely.
Xiao-Pei Duo.
What are your current
WeChat nicknames for each other?
My note for him is "Crazy Guy".
That's actually kind of cute in a way.
Super cute.
My first note for her was
"Contradiction Monster".
You call her a "Contradiction Monster"?
You're the actual
"Contradiction Monster".
I don't care.
Ms. Chunye is my voice.
He was like,
"Will you hit it?"
"No".
Then he turned around and hit it.
That was you.
You are
a "Contradiction Monster" couple.
(Locked tight)
So did you ever win in tennis later?
Yes.
- Can I say it?
- Yes, I have.
You can say it.
Go ahead.
So on the show, you lost on purpose?
You deliberately lost?
I think so.
I think he did.
I was also there off the show.
I was the referee.
I wanted to know
who is actually better
between the two of them.
(Hidden champion)
So you deliberately
wanted to be dominated.
Actually, you could win.
Such a good actor.
(Well, figure it out yourself)
So shyly calling her "sister"
was also deliberate.
(Xuan.)
(Sis.)
No.
(On purpose)
He's not being frank.
(You little rascal)
(Got caught)
What I got from the show was that
you two happened to be like this.
When one person got sensitive,
the other would step up.
When one was acting like a hedgehog,
the other would catch them.
I want to know
about your interactions after that.
Has there been a time
when you suddenly felt
both of you were sensitive
at the same time?
Actually, I am also
a highly sensitive person.
So I can capture
her thoughts.
A lot of the times,
just by looking at her expression,
a smile
or look she gives me,
I can roughly understand
what she means.
I can quickly
capture her feelings.
We both know deep down
what each other is thinking.
Actually, after leaving the house,
I also realized
that sometimes I have
moments of sensitivity.
So I've also been reflecting
and adjusting my own state.
Like how
to strengthen my sense of security
and to positively give
feedback to the other.
It's very important.
This is how I
handle my issue
of insecurity.
I just happen to have a question
for everyone,
about long-distance situations.
How are you handling it?
(Long-distance)
What is the frequency of meeting now?
Once a month.
But we
are always in touch.
We even sleep on the phone.
So it's okay.
That's quite sweet.
Us too.
We often call each other,
video calls as well.
Maybe usually,
when we are busy with work,
we'd focus on our own things.
Whenever we have time,
we call each other.
Truly in the passionate phase.
For me personally,
because of my job,
before September this year,
I have to come to Shanghai
every ten days.
So long-distance situations,
for me,
are not a big problem now.
(Breaking the long-distance obstacle)
Actually, we see each other
three times a month.
Actually, when it's more frequent,
it can be up to four times.
(Sweet)
It's like you've never been apart.
I have a question.
Actually, I saw on the show
that other groups had conflicts
or had some disagreements in ideas.
But you two
never did.
Retirement style.
Retirement-style love.
Do you have conflicts in real life?
Relatively speaking,
BK and I are quite
emotionally stable.
When we have
some differences of opinion,
we might cool down for five minutes.
(Calm down and then communicate)
Neither of us says anything.
And after five minutes,
we'll discuss the issue again.
So at your most intense moment,
you'll just cool down five minutes?
Yes, and then it's fine.
Then let me ask the Liu-Zhou duo.
Netizens say
that you are in a cycle
of fighting and making up.
Now that you are in real life,
do you still have this little cycle?
I think on the show,
it didn't count as fighting.
I think
it's still a process
of communication
and confirming
our feelings.
Actually, after we got together,
we have never fought.
Up until now,
we haven't argued.
Right.
In the house,
Youling gave me
more pressure.
Or it felt like he was asking
for an answer.
But actually, in private interactions,
he is
quite nice.
He would thoughtfully
take care of me and be considerate.
Yes.
And he shows a lot of understanding
and tolerance toward my emotions.
Yeah.
It seems Liu had
a special birthday.
Yeah.
We celebrated it together on May 20.
My birthday is on May 21.
(For details, see the extra episode)
He talked to the shop owner
and planned some surprises.
Happy birthday, baby.
When we sat down
at that seat,
I could see
"Happy birthday, Miss Liu"
on the big screen.
That's great.
For your gift-giving part
on confession night,
how long did you actually spend?
I mean, in your mind,
how did you construct it?
Actually, in the beginning,
I really saw
that her phone screen was cracked.
So I first bought the phone.
There was no progression.
Then I went to get the case
and screen protector.
The first two steps were easier.
The hardest was the third step.
Taking out the phone.
You're usually the type
who doesn't spend money.
Yes.
You'll only buy a screen protector.
- So you said the third step is hard.
- The first two steps
are something I can do.
Oh, I see.
So in the future, if someone wants
to give a screen protector
or a phone case as a gift,
they will feel pressured.
Because if they don't
follow up with more...
Wait,
that's it?
In this lifetime, everyone won't give
screen protectors and cases anymore.
I'll ask one more question
for Mr. Zhou.
For your own couple pairing,
you voted for it yourself, right?
Really?
Really.
I got caught.
- You're too cute!
- Can you explain
what you were thinking at that time?
I'm the one who revealed this.
I can tell the story.
This is especially funny.
Because of his work,
he has some phones for work
and some for personal use.
So he has two or three phones.
On the WeTV platform,
there is a couple shipping ranking.
One day,
he suddenly
said to me,
"Liu,
do you vote for your couple ranking
every day?"
I said yes.
I use up all the free chances.
As for me,
when I see it today, I'll vote for it.
Or
whenever I see it, I vote for it.
He said, "You're not working hard.
You don't work hard
for our couple pairing."
Then...
"You don't work hard."
So, every day,
he watched ads 20 times on each phone
to vote on that couple ranking.
So sweet!
Actually, last time,
he dropped his phone in a taxi.
He was very anxious that day.
He said to me,
"Baby, I lost my phone.
What should I do?
I can't watch ads and vote anymore."
("Forced love" invalidated)
So devoted.
We learned a lot of things
that we didn't have the chance
to find out on the show.
So, on the spot,
in order to get to know them better,
we are going to play
several rounds of games.
We are starting
(Couple Contest)
a competition among four couples.
The couple who loses
will receive punishment.
For the first round, our game is called
(A couple embracing from behind, Charades)
"A couple embracing from behind".
Charades.
In the observation room,
there is a very ace combination
called Welcome Guang-Lin.
(Welcome Guang-Lin)
You two can demonstrate for everyone.
How can we do that?
Come on, quickly.
Both of us?
What now?
You don't want to?
(Hesitating)
She's been waiting
for this moment in this season.
(Slowly getting up)
Wait.
I'm mainly afraid
they don't know how to play.
It's mainly for our sake.
Right.
Right?
Can this show be watched
in Taiwan, China?
(Guang's worry)
But it doesn't matter.
(Pulling him over)
Let's just sacrifice for the show a bit.
Honey, it's all for the show.
You know?
We're going to count down.
Okay.
You two, get into position.
Go for it. Thank you.
What? "Thank you"?
You want to get off work.
No.
See you next episode.
Come on.
Here we go.
Countdown begins now.
Where is it?
Behind you.
It's with Xiaowen.
(Prompt: Lady with a young vibe
and young gentleman with a mature vibe)
Well.
Three plus one plus three.
This one is a bit hard.
(Enjoying the show)
I suggest you skip this one.
Just move on to the next one.
What?
This is eight.
The first character.
Seven characters in total.
Me.
No, it's...
(This is "lady")
No, the first character is...
You.
No.
How do you...
I'll skip.
This one is way too hard.
Next one.
(Prompt: Welcome Guang-Lin)
Let's go.
Okay.
Eight characters.
Four characters.
You need to imitate
their details and gestures.
Like counting on your fingers and stuff.
Four characters.
(What does that mean?)
What is this?
Me.
You.
Just do that gesture.
It's just...
(Anxious)
What does it mean?
Four characters.
You.
Me.
Us.
Yeah.
Together.
Go.
(Out of ideas)
(Reasonable suspicion)
Is she pretending not to guess it
so she could play a little longer?
(Can't stand watching anymore)
How about letting me try?
She would guess it instantly, you know.
Come on.
If I switch with you,
she'll guess it very quickly.
You know.
I've seen through it.
This is so clumsy.
Come on.
Four characters.
It's related to us two.
Us.
Four characters, related to us two.
A lifetime of happiness together.
This is "Goodbye to you".
Welcome Guang-Lin.
Yes.
Next one.
(Prompt)
You can do it. You can do it.
This one seems doable.
A song.
The first character is...
Me.
The second character is...
Who sang this back then?
I...
Think about Xuan's Moments.
A song.
♪I think I will start to miss you♪
♪But I just met you♪
(Prompt: I think I will start to miss you,
but I just met you)
So impressive.
Impressive.
(Prompt: Catfish, are you stuck?)
Six characters.
The first character is...
Big?
Not "big". What "big"?
Look at this.
What does this mean?
Separate? Open?
Sticky?
Yes.
Catfish?
Yes, and then?
Catfish Effect?
Catfish. The first character is still...
Catfish?
The second character is...
It's a question.
Catfish, sticky.
(People really do laugh
when they are speechless)
You can just whisper it to her.
Catfish,
are you stuck?
What?
She can't hear you.
Catfish,
are you stuck?
Catfish, are you stuck?
- Impressive.
Next one.
(Prompt: Does the perfume smell good)
Guess it. Four characters.
You must guess.
Smell it.
Does the perfume smell good?
We killed the game.
(Exiting in glory)
Awesome. This is so great.
These four characters.
Just now,
how many questions
did our team get right?
Getting it right
doesn't matter, does it?
The key is the process.
(A difficult process)
Next, each couple
will do it in the same way
as they did just now.
Which pair wants to go first?
Let's do it.
So nervous.
I'll...
I'll stand over here.
Okay, timer starts now.
(Countdown)
(Reverse parking)
(Holding tight)
Look quickly.
Stop touching.
(Prompt: Reverse parking)
Don't hold her hands so fiercely.
He's holding her hands
and rubbing them.
We are...
Driving.
Reversing.
- Reverse parking.
- Four characters.
(Prompt: Archery)
Archery.
(Prompt: Seaside fireworks)
Fireworks.
Four characters.
Seaside. Seaside fireworks.
You two just click.
(Prompt: Cover with a blanket)
When I sleep, you...
Three characters.
I snore?
What?
When do you snore?
We heard it.
Someone snores.
On me, you...
Cover with a blanket.
That's right.
Next one.
(Prompt: Secret)
What?
Just demonstrate it directly,
I think.
Just demonstrate it.
- Three characters.
- Locking kiss.
Locking kiss.
(Prompt: Neck-grabbing kiss)
No, there's a...
(Countdown)
Two characters first.
Neck-grabbing kiss.
Time's up.
(Wang Yi, Lu Bingkun: 6 questions)
You are so amazing.
So impressive.
Well, BK,
do you know where you fell short?
Well,
when the game started just now,
you were still touching her hands.
Yeah, you were caught up
in touching her hands.
I was a little stuck.
A little stuck.
Come on.
Come on, Xiao-Pei Duo.
This team is definitely
going to be hilarious.
I'm already laughing.
Two masters of saying the opposite, huh?
They turn four characters into eight.
Not wanting to win, eight characters.
Okay.
Come on. Timer starts now.
(Countdown: two minutes)
(Prompt: Wake surfing)
Surfing.
- Four characters.
- Wake surfing.
Very fast.
(Prompt: Playing tennis)
Playing tennis.
(Prompt: Playing the trumpet)
Playing the trumpet.
Four characters.
(Hit)
Trumpet playing.
Yeah.
(Prompt: Headlock hug)
Three characters.
Head pat.
Head hold.
And one more character.
Headlock hug.
Yes.
(Prompt: Riding an e-bike)
Injured, my leg hurts so much.
Injured?
Because of what? Four characters.
Riding an e-bike.
(Answer: Holding an umbrella)
Okay.
Holding an umbrella.
(Prompt: Putting in eye drops)
- Putting in eye drops.
- Okay.
So impressive.
Look at their chemistry.
(Prompt: Secret)
I can't see.
What?
It's hard for us to help you with this.
(Unable to help)
Your last sentence on Confession Night.
I like you.
Me. Plus my name.
Xiao Wentao, I like you.
(Prompt: Xiao Wentao, I like you)
(Prompt: Popcorn)
The movie was good, and then I want
to eat something. Three characters.
Something you eat at the cinema.
Popcorn.
Yes.
(Prompt: Peppa Pig)
Me, you, me.
Peppa Pig.
It's a repeated one.
No more questions.
(Xiao Wentao and Jia Peixuan: 10 questions)
We're too amazing.
We cleared it.
They answered all our questions.
Impressive.
So impressive.
Headlock hug.
It directly...
Blew the hairstyle off.
Sorry.
- Thank you.
- Is that okay?
It's okay.
A real couple is just different.
They're just different.
It proves you two are cleared.
You two are fake.
Yeah, we two are cleared.
Almost.
Come on, you two get into position.
Start.
(Prompt: Touching abs)
Touch my...
Abs.
(Off to a bad start)
You said that character.
(Can't say the character on the card)
Never mind, next one.
(Prompt: Face holding)
What is this?
Like this, two characters.
And then...
Like this.
Three characters in total.
This is for the first two characters.
And this is for the last character.
(Straining the whole body)
(You know?)
Say it.
Face touching.
Almost there. Got it.
(Prompt: Teasing the kitten)
And then...
Ice Cream.
Teasing the cat.
Three characters.
Cat teaser.
The last is a pet's name.
What pet's name?
What is Ice Cream?
Teasing the cat.
Cat.
(Outside help)
Nickname.
Teasing the kitty. Teasing the kitten.
(Prompt: Husband vibe)
You said something about me.
At my place,
when I was cooking,
(Baby)
Baby, hurry.
Husband.
Husband vibe.
Yes.
(Prompt: Neck holding)
Three characters. The last one is this.
We just mentioned it.
And then...
Holding.
Yes, and then...
And then, this is the second one.
Grab the neck.
Change the first character.
Choke the neck.
- Change it again.
- The first one.
- Change the first character again.
- Slit the neck.
- Hold the neck.
- Okay.
Right. Next one.
(Heart gesture)
(Answer: Strolling in Xiamen)
When we
went back to my hometown,
and after we finished eating...
Taking a walk.
The city, and then...
- Xiamen.
- Yes.
Walking in Xiamen.
change the third character.
Running in Xiamen. No.
(Countdown)
You do what I do.
(Slow)
Sliding.
Sliding in Xiamen.
Time's up.
(Yang Xihui and Ling Lizheng:
4 Questions)
- Alright.
- What is that?
Strolling.
Oh, no. It's over.
Come on.
Which way? Facing this way?
You can start now. Get ready.
(Shy)
The two-minute countdown starts now.
(Countdown: two minutes)
You can look now.
(Prompt: Playing the piano)
Three characters.
A musical instrument.
Playing the piano.
(Prompt: Fishing)
Two characters.
Fishing.
(Prompt: Ring toss)
Two characters.
(Hint)
Blue puppy.
Ring toss.
Yes.
(Prompt: Old Fox)
Three characters. My nickname.
Nickname?
You mentioned it on the show.
Old Fox.
(Impressed)
Such great chemistry.
Next one.
(Prompt: Secret)
This is so hard.
This is way too hard.
Five characters.
The first two characters are...
(Bossy CEO)
The first two characters are "bossy CEO"?
Bossy CEO.
Change the form of address.
What's your name?
Liu.
- The first character is...
- Liu.
The second character is...
Liu Zhou.
Change it again.
- Liu's Uncle.
- Liu's Uncle?
What is "Liu's Uncle"?
Uncle?
Change it again.
Liu...
(Anxious)
Change it to something more...
more intimate.
B-Boyfriend?
No, Liu what?
Liu's Husband.
So smart.
The last two characters are right,
Liu's Husband's head-pat.
Yes, and then...
The last character is...
Liu's Husband's head-pat gesture.
Every team's "gesture" is different.
Quick, hurry up.
(Prompt: Whispering)
You can do it.
(Instilling faith)
Three characters.
(Substitute for shyness)
(Pleasing to the eye)
(Loving to watch)
(Totally hooked)
Three characters.
Whispering.
(Shy)
(Answer: Teasing the puppy)
We can stall for time.
Three characters.
What is Brother?
- A puppy.
- Yes.
H-Hooking the puppy.
No.
What is it?
What is this?
(Countdown)
Teasing the puppy.
Yes.
Time's up.
(Zhou Youling and Xu Lvyang:
7 Questions)
- Very impressive.
- So impressive.
Then let's invite
the group with the lowest score
in this round to come up.
(Ling-Xi Duo takes the punishment)
Us?
It seems so.
The couple needs
to pass the tissue mouth-to-mouth.
Passing the tissue is like this.
Passing the tissue
may sound pretty boring.
What's so special
about passing the tissue?
But it's like this.
(A little bit)
Just a little bit.
This is a bit flustering.
I'll hold it.
(A tiny little bit)
Okay, this little bit is enough.
You guy.
Lizheng, I see it now.
Just like this.
Very good.
Quick, pass the tissue.
She caught it.
(Liu's Husband is envious)
Help!
I just blamed myself
for tearing off too big a piece.
Then Lizheng tore it off again.
Yeah.
This is
the first round, the warm-up game.
This next one
is
lifting the seal of love.
Here are the rules.
The other three guys
will stick 20 sticky notes
on the guy participating in this game.
The girl can only use her mouth
to tear them off.
No hands.
(So thrilling)
And in the end
whoever takes the longest time
will receive the punishment.
Which group wants to go first?
Let's go first then.
- Come on.
(Volunteering)
The other guys can stick them on me.
Come on, other guys,
stick them on him however you want.
(Let's begin)
(Starting it off)
Come on, hurt each other.
Stick 20 on first, okay?
(Observing)
Stick 20 above the shoulder line.
Stick 20 on his mouth.
- Stick 20 on the lips.
- Lips.
Not sticking any on the mouth?
He's very talkative.
(Mischievous idea brewing)
I'm going to stick some on his tongue.
(Mouth shut)
They're all sticking them on his mouth
and face.
Youling, you do know how to stick them.
(Behind the ear)
Ears, nose, and stuff.
Eyelids.
(Positions get trickier)
(Xiao adds one too)
(I'll stick it wherever Youling does)
Where? Where did he stick it?
He stuck it inside his ear hole.
(Begging for compliments)
Xiaowen, you have to remember
they'll stick them on you next.
(Taking mental notes)
I'm keeping track.
I'm holding back.
I won't stick them particularly...
20 yet?
(One last sticker before leaving)
The rest are all yours.
(Behaving)
(Checking on her byba)
Let me take a look first.
Lost a "beard hair".
Lost one.
Okay, that's 20.
How many are you going to stick?
20.
(Catch the bossy CEO's love)
(Liu is helpless)
Zhou Youling.
Zhou Youling has love for BK.
(Face full of love)
(Exiting with satisfaction)
Get ready.
Timer starts now.
There are more on the neck. On the neck.
Right side of the neck.
So this game is this fun.
It's even more fun with eyes closed.
It's because she...
(Don't talk. Learn carefully)
Ruita is so fast.
I think Ruita
sees only the game when playing a game.
Eyes only on the task.
So fast.
She can be so fast?
A little reward at the end.
All gone.
Finished.
(Wang Yi and Lu Bingkun: 34.93s)
Ruita was so fast.
Amazing.
34.93 seconds.
They went all out.
(Smiling)
Come on, next one.
(Not smiling)
(Hidden in the hair)
(That's too much)
Lu Bingkun.
- You little rascal.
- No way.
Should we go earlier?
(It needs to be early)
It gets harder as it gets later.
He's so "evil".
So in this game,
you have to be first.
(Continuing mischief)
Yes, the later it gets, the worse it is.
Isn't your hair just perfect for it?
(Sticking on top of the head)
- That's way too much.
- Lu Bingkun.
He hid it.
- He hid it in his hair.
- Ruita.
(Keep your byba in check)
BK is now
extremely happy.
(What about me?)
Are there 20 already?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5,
6, 7, 8, 9, 10,
11, 12,
13, 14, 15,
16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
Enough. There's one more
on the top of the head.
Ready? We're about to start the timer.
Come on. Timer starts now.
Why do I feel like Ling Lizheng
is enjoying it?
He's secretly enjoying it.
The corner of his mouth is lifting.
Why is Ling Lizheng
enjoying it?
Ling Lizheng is deliberately
not cooperating, isn't he?
I'm very cooperative.
There's one here.
Here.
Hui, here.
It's over. It took forever.
Great.
Got a mouthful of hair.
This is so hard for us.
My lipstick is all rubbed off.
1 minute and 44 seconds.
(Yang Xihui and Ling Lizheng: 104s)
My mouth's so bitter.
He got stuck in so many tricky spots.
A real challenge.
Who's next?
(Anxious)
You.
Go quickly.
I'll go.
(Seizing the initiative)
If you go last,
you'll get the worst of it.
Can BK
play another round?
Why?
That's why
he went first.
Come on, 20.
Can you guys go easy on him?
I'll be nicer to you.
I didn't stick them on you guys
that harshly just now.
Guaranteed not harsh.
You sealed Xiaowen's mouth shut.
Youling, first count how many there are.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
Help.
Xiaowen, you usually might not be too...
You talk too much.
(Leaving you speechless)
Is that enough?
Come on, Xuan.
Come on. Timer starts now.
Xiaowen is so happy
that his dimples are showing again.
Xiaowen, don't smirk.
Xiaowen's dimples
are formed just like this.
Xiaowen is holding back laughter.
Holding back laughter.
Holding it in hard.
Don't you dare enjoy it.
Don't you dare enjoy it too much.
This game is really not bad.
Really.
I quite like this game.
Then I'll take the sticky notes back
and find my husband...
Don't bend down so far.
There are more on top of his head.
This is definitely from BK.
Buried in the "texture".
She's eating all the dandruff.
This...
Top of his head.
Forehead.
There's a simple one left.
Okay, finished.
It fell off.
(Jia Peixuan and Xiao Wentao: 73s)
1 minute and 13 seconds.
Wentao, when you're with Xuan,
are you easily shy in private?
It's okay, I guess.
It's okay.
It's...
It's okay, I guess.
I'll stick them myself.
Quick, stick them on him.
You can't stick them yourself.
Are you kidding?
You stick them yourself?
(Finally got you)
You have to remember
how he treated you back then.
after you stick them on him,
he can't stick them back on you.
(Truth)
He's the last.
Stick them on.
Stick them on his gums.
Does it have to be this precise?
On the gums?
Nostrils.
(Got it)
One for the nostril.
Xiaowen really stuck it on his nostril.
(Couldn't hold back)
It's itchy.
How many? Let me count.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
Every spot is meticulously designed.
(Liu can't handle it)
Really, I'm speechless.
How about you get two tears for him?
It's 20 now, right?
(Giving advice)
Just make him squat down a bit.
It'll be fast.
One more is enough.
Enough, that's 20.
Okay.
Feels like it's gone over.
Squat down, squat down.
Squat.
Three, two, one, go.
Is this how you play it?
Tear off with your mouth.
These two have
a really strong desire to win.
(Already stunned)
They're here to win the game.
Don't pull his hair off.
(Painful expression)
Mr. Zhou's bangs
split apart visibly.
Hairstylist.
Liu only wants to win.
Liu's eyes see only victory and defeat.
Front of the neck.
Use your teeth.
Is your neck itchy or what?
Liu took a bite
toward Mr. Zhou's forehead.
She launched a fierce attack.
Too fierce.
Did you get a mouthful of hair?
How long?
(Zhou Youling and Xu Lvyang: 105s)
1 minute and 45 seconds?
They thought the time went fast
because they were enjoying it.
It actually took a long time.
Okay, so that means
you accept the loss.
Right?
So,
for the Zhou-Liu duo,
we've customized a little punishment.
It's to have them use this dialogue
(Punishment 1: Bossy CEO Lines Act)
called "Bossy CEO Lines"
to act out as a duo.
This is so perfect for you two.
This is simply tailor-made for you.
Are they like this on a daily basis?
There's no need to act, right?
Yeah, these are their usual lines.
Or, if you think this way
isn't spicy enough,
you can reverse it.
That is, Liu is the bossy CEO.
(Becomes the bossy CEO)
(Becomes the female lead)
Mr. Zhou is the female lead. It'll do.
This is fun to watch.
Actually, this isn't hard for Liu.
But it's hard for Zhou Youling.
Yeah.
Do you want the normal version first,
or the gender-swapped version first?
We can do the normal version first.
The normal version first?
Okay, come on.
(Bossy CEO: Zhou Youling, Female Lead: Xu Lvyang)
Woman, you are the first one who dares
to speak to me like this.
Let me go.
I beg you, let me go, okay?
If you are deliberately
trying to provoke me,
I'm telling you,
you've succeeded.
You're so easily swayed by me.
It's quite cute actually.
Reverse it.
Let's not, okay?
Just this one take.
Reverse it.
(Shy)
Isn't there another line below?
There isn't, right?
You really want
to be in a drama, don't you?
He wants to play
the bossy CEO a bit longer.
Yeah, it needs to have context.
Reverse it
in a really exciting way.
Okay.
Come on.
(Immediately gets into character)
Look.
Liu...
Liu likes it.
Youling, your posture is too...
You need to be more petite.
You have to...
You have to do this.
Legs together.
(Well-behaved)
(Female Lead: Zhou Youling, Bossy CEO: Xu Lvyang)
You are the first one
who dares to speak to me like this.
Let me go.
I beg you, okay?
If you are deliberately
trying to provoke me,
I'm telling you, you've succeeded.
You're so easily swayed by me.
It's quite cute actually.
The reversed version is more like them.
The reversed version works.
(Punishment 2: Cutesy-Voice Couple Talk)
Cutesy-voice couple talk.
Please imitate me.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Each person says one line.
If you love me, stay with me.
She'll say it alone?
It's mutual.
Each person says one line.
Master class from Ms. Sie.
How satisfying.
Isn't this a reward for you?
If you love me, stay with me.
Okay, your turn.
If you love me, give me a kiss-kiss.
(Under everyone's watch)
Give me that cutesy voice.
Eight eyes are watching you.
(On the spot)
If you love me, kiss me.
Kiss-kiss.
The cutesy voice.
You didn't use the cutesy voice.
If you love me, give me a kiss-kiss.
Okay, the girl's turn.
If you love me, compliment me.
Hand gesture.
Okay, the guy's hand gesture.
Do this. Your voice doesn't pass.
Your hand gesture must pass.
Okay.
If you love me, hug me.
(As expected of Ms. Evonne)
Impressive.
Okay.
Let's give a round of applause
to the four couples.
Thank you all.
We ship you.
Yeah, we ship you.
Actually, everyone here
is very, very familiar with you.
Because we've watched
your interaction in the house
for almost a month.
I believe these 26 days
should have a very extraordinary meaning
for each and every one of you.
So could each of you
share what
this Love Actually S5 journey
means
to you?
Although it seems like
the house journey has ended,
I think
for us,
(Both an end and a beginning)
it's a new starting point.
Because we are about
to return to reality
and face many
real, tangible aspects of life,
like interactions and adjustments.
Yeah, like Ruita said,
after leaving the house,
we'll enter reality
and face
challenges in life
and all other sorts of things.
But I believe
if we both have a common goal
and
can help each other,
we'll keep going further on this path.
I think the biggest feeling for me
is that while recording this show,
from a different person's perspective,
I observe myself and felt,
"So this is the state I'm in."
I think it's quite interesting too.
For me,
the 26-day life
in the house is actually
very, very special.
It's my first time living together
with 12 people.
I fell off a bike the first time.
With all the things that happened,
for me,
I feel like I've grown a lot.
Yes.
Actually, our show
has only ten episodes in total,
and there are 12 people in total.
There might
not be enough time for everyone.
What you see
is only part of who we are.
So I hope you can
get to know us more.
Each one of us
is a very multi-dimensional
and very lovely person.
I'll try hard.
I hope the happy ending
will come as expected.
For all the things that happened
in these 26 days,
to summarize their meaning to me,
it's a very simple sentence:
If one day I lose my memory,
I will watch Love Actually S5 again.
Yeah.
The two of us were joking one day.
It seemed like...
What was I doing that day?
I seemed to hit my head.
I felt dizzy for a moment.
And I said to him,
"Oh, no.
I think I'm having amnesia."
He said...
His first reaction was to say,
"Then what if you can't remember me?"
Then he quickly added, "It's okay.
You can watch Love Actually S5."
From the day we met
to us falling in love,
Love Actually S5
has recorded it all.
Well said.
Then, all members
of the observation team,
can we send them
our sincere blessings?
Okay, I'll go first.
Actually, I most
want to send my blessings
to Wentao and Xuan.
I feel like my husband and I
are both people
who have experienced
a lot of heartbreak.
It felt like when all the tragedies
were falling towards you,
and you were becoming the next tragedy,
you happened to meet someone,
and you decided
to stop the domino effect together
(Overthrowing the pain)
and fall to the other side instead.
The opposite direction
that heads towards happiness.
I think that's a wonderful thing.
I believe you will both
fall towards happiness.
Thank you.
I'll first
send a blessing to Liu
and Zhou.
As the saying goes:
if you love the right person,
every day is Valentine's Day.
I wish that every day for you
from now on
can be
as sweet as your
first official date.
I'd like to say something
to BK and Ruita.
You are poised and graceful.
It isn't about decency
in the broad sense
or fulfilling others.
It's about
constantly improving yourselves
and using more refined senses
to embrace this world and each other.
So I hope you two
can continue to be this happy forever.
And meanwhile,
hold on to your
own thoughts and beliefs.
Okay.
Thank you.
I want to say something to Hui
and Ling Lizheng.
You must believe
that the power of attraction
is actually very strong.
It's also the essence of love.
So I'll be rooting
for you both,
and I wish you all the best.
Thank you, Ms. Shen.
Everyone has given the four couples
some blessings.
From my perspective,
I especially hope,
on behalf of the production team
and all the members
of the observation team,
to thank the four couples
who came here today.
At the same time,
I think we should also
thank the four who couldn't be here:
Jianying, Danqi, Zhuoran,
and Ji Yu.
Thank you for sharing with us
your stories and memories
from this summer,
which are so important.
Then, I especially hope
that the four couples here
can remember well
the names of every one of our observers
and also
our guests on Love Actually S5.
They are Dong Xuan, Xu Mengtao,
Zhang Zining, Xu Zhisheng,
and Meng Yutong.
Because remembering these names means
that from now on,
whenever you are in need,
I hope you will think of these names.
You should know that in this world,
there is a place
where we are sending you
our eternal and best wishes.
Thank you.
There are 365 days in a year.
We send you 365 blessings.
At the same time, we also want to thank
all the viewers
who have been watching
and accompanying
Love Actually S5 on WeTV.
Thank you for your support.
Restores hair shaft protein
from the root.
Lasting resilience and shine
for three days.
This show is sponsored
by Pantene Pro-V Foam Shampoo.
Let's thank once again
all our friends
and all the staff members.
See you next season.
Thank you.
Well said.
(Preview)
What do you want to order?
Teasing me?
I'll bite you.
Alright.
I'm fine.
Are you trying to pinch me to death?
Is your hotel bed uncomfortable?
Maybe we should change hotels tonight.
Babe, last night you stole the blanket
when rolling over.
I often steal the blanket.
In the morning, I had no blanket.
You'd shoved me to the edge.
Good.
Babe,
I'll put the glasses in your bag.
The back of your head is flat again.
It's okay.
This is what makes it handmade.
This is what makes it unique.
Oh, no.
It's fine, babe.
This is what makes it handmade.
Babe, we're now in the big city.
So awesome.
We've made it to the big city.
Let's go to the dye workshop in Wuzhen.
And experience it.
Weave it for me.
Where is your heart?
Bottom right corner.
Give another kiss, you two.
Like this?
Look up.
No.
(Paid content only for SVVVVVVVIP)
We're back.
At the end, I said,
"Xiao Wentao, I like you."
Are you happy?
I am happy.
Look at the atmosphere.
Hi.
Get married!
Let me introduce her.
This is my girlfriend.
Anyone else to introduce?
Congratulations.
Be happy.
Thank you.
Production team.
Well, what's with this dubbing?
Xuan's emotional value
is off the charts.
Bossy CEO.
Looks like you just got off work.
You just got off work.
You're married.
Now give us a live version.
(Guide to Love Actually S5
Finale Celebration Banquet)